# Andrés Moisés Camhi Ventura

Haim Ben Atar 17, Tel Aviv linkedin.com/in/amcamhi/ +972 587851689 andrescamhi@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

Business Administration and Economics professional of *Universidad Católica de Chile*. Proactive, team player, creative and fast learner. With 3+ years of professional experience gained working in Customer Success and Sales divisions in the SAAS industry, acquiring valuable skills into implementing and optimizing digital marketing campaigns, copywriting, enterprise sales and account management. Keen to be part of an outstanding team with people of excellence, with a strong ethical sense, and having a high-impact job with accelerated learning, which will provide opportunities for further growth and progression.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Account Executive**

Sept 2019 – June 2020

Optimove

- End to end B2B Sales, built and nurtured new customer relationships from prospect to closure, with medium to enterprise size companies in LATAM and Spain.
- Delivered Web-based and in-person sales presentations and demonstrations of variable technical complexity, in 3 languages, to C-Level executives and management levels of customer organizations, responding to changing business needs
- Attended conferences, meetings and networking events in LATAM, Spain and the US, generating quality business opportunities.

SDR

Nov 2018 - Aug 2019

Optimove

- Top performing SDR in terms of opportunities created across the company
- Drove outbound lead generation efforts in LATAM, Iberian Peninsula and South Africa, with different sales enablement tools
- Created effective sales sequences and automations for different verticals and customer personas
- Booked and conducted business meetings with management level and decision-makers in over 100 medium to enterprise size companies in my assigned territories

# **Customer Success Manager**

Sept 2017 - July 2018

Keywee

- Day-to-day campaign management of high budget (\$150k+ monthly)
   Facebook Ads campaigns for top-tier publishers and strategic accounts, for several use cases
- POC for all customer needs
- Provided data-driven reports on campaign progress, KPI's, audiences and insights for improving performance
- Onboarding new customers Kickoff calls, managing new customers through CRM software, implementation of marketing pixels and training on the product's reporting dashboard and capabilities
- Customer retention and upselling Customer calls, discussion of insights, price and content trends, and alternatives to improve KPI's

#### **SKILLS**

#### Computer

MS Office (Advanced)
Facebook Ads (Advanced)
Photoshop (Intermediate)
CRM (Salesforce/Hubspot)
Apollo.io (Sales Platform)
Linkedin Sales Navigator

#### Languages

Spanish (Native)
English (Fluent)
Hebrew (Intermediate)
Portuguese (Intermediate)

#### **COURSES**

#### **University Electives**

Product and Branding Strategy
Integrated Marketing Communications
Design Thinking
Topics in Corporate Finances
Design Bootcamp

#### **INTERESTS**

Fantasy Football Travel Reading Business Innovation Guitar Playing

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Maximum Score in Mathematics PSU Honorary Scholarship for academic excellence – Universidad Católica de Chile

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Nationality: Chilean

Date of birth: 23 - March - 1993

## **COMPLEMENTARY EXPERIENCE**

Maccabi Hatzair Chile (2001-2014)

Jewish Youth Movement

• Responsible for the formation of future leaders of the local Jewish community

# Machon Le Madrichim (1st Semester of 2012)

•Jerusalem based program, focused on strengthen youth leadership

# **EDUCATION**

**UNIVERSITY** Universidad Católica de Chile (2011 - 2016)

**Faculty of Economic and Administrative Sciences** 

BSc in Business Administration and Economics

**SCHOLAR** Instituto Hebreo Dr. Chaim Weizmann (Class of 2010)